simicart.com 2016-05-04

# Privacy Policy | SimiCart.Com

## Privacy Policy

At [SimiCart](http://www.simicart.com/ "Simicart - Magento Mobile App Builder") we recognize that privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. We assume that you accept our policy when you sign up and use our services.

**Information Collected**

When you visit [http://www.simicart.com](http://www.simicart.com/ "Simicart - Magento mobile app builder"), we collect your IP address and web browser information. If you want to create an account at http://www.simicart.com/, we require that you provide your personal information: name, address and email address. When you use SimiCart’s products and services, you may need to give us some additional information: address, phone, website and website platform.

**How we use your information**

Our main purpose in collecting your information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient experience when you browse our site. We use this information to process and deliver your order, for billing purposes, for providing a more pleasant and personalized shopping experience, and for communicating with you about orders and promotional updates. You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging in your account and going to the My Account section.

**How we use cookies**

When you access our website, we may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer. This data contains information about you and it helps us to identify you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don’t need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out your account or close your browser, this cookie expires and won't affect your computer. If you disable cookies for our site, you may still use our site, but certain aspects of your shopping experience with us may be affected.

**How we protect and store personal information**

We are committed to protecting personal information. We store your information on our secure server. We use SSL for the checkout process, helping you keep your billing information safe. No credit card information is saved on our system. We don’t share your personal information with any other parties.

You can always trust that when you do business with SimiCart, we always try our best to protect our customers.

**Changes to privacy policy**

Please note that our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. SimiCart reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy at any time. Regardless, we will post any changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through the web site.
